I won't fall for you.
You're just a Pig's Foot.
Makabe Masamune at his
absolute best yet again today.
I am truly like the rising sun!
Yikes, guess you're still full of yourself.
Gah!
Chinatsu! I thought I told you
not to just barge in here!
Yeah, whatever. Man, you're loud.
Control yourself when you're in France.
Don't embarrass all of Japan.
Class Trip  France
Yasaka High School
Good morning, Maa-kun and Chinatsu-chan!
It's time for breakfast.
You're leaving today, aren't you?
I went all-out for you today!
There's fried chicken,
fried shrimp, and even gratin!
High in calories
Yay, gratin!
Maa-kun, is there anything
else you'd like to ea—
Both of you, out!
Damn that loli hag...
How could I eat something so high
in calories first thing in the morning?
The greatest opportunity since the
cultural festival has presented itself!
The City of Flowers is truly a perfect
place to exact my revenge.
And that's when I'll get a checkmate
in my Dead or Love plan!
Are you ready, Aki-sama?
Yes.
Could you take my suitcase, Yoshino?
As you wish.
Get me a gift, 'kay thanks.
Maa-kun, come home soon, okay?
Maa-kun!
Yeah, yeah. I'll see you later.
#1 "The Wee Parisian Mademoiselle"
Dearest Muriel, I saw the piece you sent me.
It's quite a masterpiece.
One piece of advice I have for you:
you should learn more about
Japanese high school students.
So it is hopeless.
No matter how much I practice...
High school students from Japon...
They're just too far away.
Wow...
An art museum was made in the
Louvre Palace during the French Revolution.
It can easily be called the
greatest art museum in the world.
Traveling Through France
Sans crème s'il vous plait...
"Without whipped cream, please."
I've never seen Kojuurou
study so hard in his life.
What should I do, Makabe-kun?
We're in the land of macarons,
canelés, and bon bon chocolats!
Can you believe it?!
Try to calm down a bit, Kojuurou.
Fashion! The Opera House! Ballet!
Love and romance! Amore!
What you're trying to say is...
What you're trying to say
is "amour," Futaba-san.
"Amore" is Italian.
So you've come, Cruel Princess.
Aki-chan, there was a
churros shop over there.
And there's the bumpkin fiancé.
There he goes, getting in my way again.
No, no. Calm down.
For me, this class trip should be—
We're definitely in the land of amour!
PDA everywhere!
This country is truly the best place for this.
I'm going to make Adagaki Aki fall for me,
and then dump her on the spot.
So that I can move my
Dead or Love plan forward!
Just you wait, Cruel Princess!
The rising sun...
No, Soleil le Vant!
Hey.
Huh?
Could you keep some time open
during our free periods on this trip?
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what it sounds like.
I've been thinking ever
since the cultural festival
that I should actually take some
time to properly talk to you.
Th-This is... Wait, what the heck's going on?
Anyway, this is a promise!
I'll make you pay if you break it!
U-Uh, w-wait—
O-Oh, no! A French girl?
Hey!
H-How do I apologize?
Schedule Book
Translation
Excusez moi!
Ca nefaitrien.
An eyepatch?
Are you Japonais?
Did she just speak Japanese?
Y-Yes, I'm Japanese. I'm in high school.
A high school student...
Japanese...
Yes! You're the one I was
looking for, my Chikuwa-kun!
My name is Muriel Besson!
I am a second-year in high school.
I'm Makabe Masamune.
I'm Adagaki Aki.
Your Japanese is very good.
Did you study it somewhere?
Why, yes! I learned a lot from
anime and manga from Japon, I did!
Manga, eh?
Manga from Japon is fantastic!
Every time my brother goes to Tokyo for work,
I ask him to buy me lots of manga!
She's...
...definitely an otaku.
I hope that one day I'll be able
to draw manga like that, I do.
Wait, you?
Well, we do have bande dessinée in France.
But what I want to draw is
Japonais manga, it is!
You drew this?
Yes! I still have much to work on, but...
Leave it to Tsumire
I want to draw a poppy and exciting rom-com
about Tsumire-san, who lives in Tokyo!
Rom-com?!
Why in the world are the names of the
heroine and hero Tsumire and Chikuwa?
Because my favorite Japanese food is oden!
Does something seem off to you?
I'm not sure if "off" is the right word...
I do have a lot of questions...
My older brother also told me
that I should learn more about
Japanese high school students.
When I first saw you, I thought Chikuwa-kun
was standing right in front of me!
Huh?
You're the ideal Japanese
high school boy, Masamune.
Please let me use you
as a model for my manga!
What?!
What?
What do real high school boys think about?
Do you prefer toast for breakfast?
Or perhaps sushi?
Um...
Yes?
I'm flattered that you're so interested,
but I'm currently on vacation...
Is there any way you'd consider it?
What do I do?
Hey, are you saying you don't care
about your promise with me?
I'm sorry, Muriel-san.
We're but humble high school
students on their class trip.
Humble?
Oh, you mean like the samurai?
No.
A-Anyway, we have to stay with our class,
so we don't have much free time,
and when I do, I plan to go around with her.
Hey! What's the big idea?
Throw me a bone here!
So, even though I'd like to help
you out, I just don't have time.
I'm really sorry.
I see...
I cannot force you, I cannot.
I'll be rooting for you. Good luck.
Fujinomiya-san, do you like that painting?
Yes, though I'm not sure if
"like" is the right word.
I just feel uneasy looking at it.
Look, they're not wearing anything on top.
Oh, right.
Feeling cold can lead to many ailments.
I want to lend them something to wear.
Fujinomiya-san's so nice...
Oh, yeah, Fujinomiya-san!
Yes?
Um, um, um...
You're looking quite pale
yourself, Kojuurou-san.
No! I'm totally fine.
Oh?
What's the matter, you two?!
Can someone get us some stretchers?
Mind your own business, Commando.
I don't want to excite them any more.
"Them"?
We're safe here, aren't we?
Yeah, it looks like it.
I thought I was going to die...
She sure was strange.
I'll say that she's definitely passionate.
Anyway, get off of me already!
Whoa...
S-Sorry...
Makabe.
Venez.
Adagaki-san, is your French decent?
I can basically say, "Can I get the check,"
and "Is there anyone who understands Japanese?"
Good. We're on the same level.
Why are you relieved
right now?! Are you stupid?
M-Marcy bocut!
Crowassant!
Escargoo!
Arch of Triumph! Huh?
It's a pleasure to meet you, 3D Chikuwa-kun.
My name is Frank Besson.
I'm the older brother of the
girl you just rejected, Muriel.
My position is the reverse of yours right now.
I'm actually in Tokyo on business.
Japan sure is a nice place.
B-Business, you say?
No matter. That's not the
issue here. It's what you did.
Why did you decline Muriel's request?
Huh? Uh...
The worst sin you can commit
in this world is making Muriel cry.
The second-worst sin you can commit
in this world is disappointing Muriel!
If you want to stay with that girl there,
how about you two teach Muriel
the essence of a rom-com?
That's simple enough, isn't it, Chikuwa-kun?
Ah... So when you get a day with free time,
you have to spend it with Aki-sama
and this otaku mademoiselle.
Can I ask how that happened?
I honestly have no idea.
I'm sorry. Everything was ruined despite
you setting it all up for me, Master.
Me? What did I do?
You didn't?
I figured the Cruel Princess
wouldn't invite me to talk to her
one-on-one without your help...
Seriously?
Wait, does that mean she invited me herself?
I'm honestly surprised myself.
I should actually take some
time to properly talk to you.
She looked pretty serious...
But it's a good thing that
Aki-sama seems proactive.
R-Right...
I'll help you out so that
no one else gets in your way.
Thanks.
Oh, sorry. Kojuurou and the
others are waiting for me.
Master.
I'm seriously counting on you.
How long are you gonna be in
the shower? Get out already, Gasou.
Sorry. Just hang on a little longer.
Jeez, I can't even get changed
in peace. How annoying.
Aki-chan, there was a churros shop over there.
Why don't we go there together?
Sorry, I've got something to do.
Makabe Masamune.
You accursed man.
I need money, damn it...
So that I can preserve the Gasou name and status.
Love and gender don't matter.
Money is everything.
I catch a red snapper using a shrimp...
Nay, I'll catch money using love.
I call this brilliant plan... "Fishing."
I guess neither of us got any sleep.
Okay, let's go, Adagaki-san.
Right...
Are you really okay?
Weren't you threatened
by some really scary people?
Want us to tag along quietly?
I think we'll be fine...
We're counting on you if we don't
make it back in time, Commando.
Masamune! Aki!
You actually came, you did!
I was so excited for today that
I was tingling with excitement!
Do you mean "trembling with excitement"?
Oui!
She's so serious about this...
Ah, well...
Okay, let's begin.
First, Besson-san...
You can call me Muriel.
Okay, Muriel.
There's something I want to
ask you about this manga.
Really?
First, this right here.
He asked her out three panels ago,
and they're totally a thing now.
Is there a problem with that?
As someone who's read all the volumes of
the monumental classic of romance manga,
"Rose-eyed Steroid," let me say...
When it comes to rom-coms...
Once they both fall for each other,
80% of the story is over!
Tease! Tease until you can tease no more!
Tease?
Yes.
You can make it all count in the remaining 20%,
but it's a cruel path that
I cannot recommend to beginners.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
But why?!
I mean, they like each other, right?
Then they should tell each other.
Staring at each other like this
and kissing might also be good.
Hey!
Je t'adore.
Wait, wait, wait!
Unlike French people, normal Japanese people
can't easily tell someone
else their feelings!
There are times we want to
be honest, but we can't!
Or something from their past
might be holding them back.
A lot can happen.
So even if you have feelings for each other,
there's some reason you can't tell them?
Yes, exactly!
Are you talking about you two?
A-A-A-A-A-Are you stupid?!
Aki, your Japanese is hard to understand
because you speak so fast, it is.
I'm telling you that's inconceivable!
Anyway!
What you need to learn is
the Japanese form of love.
You are forbidden from becoming
romantically involved with someone.
Understood?
I understand, I do.
We'll show you how things are done
as characters in a rom-com,
so make sure you pay attention.
Huh?
Yes! I'm looking forward to this, yes!
Honestly. You're so illogical.
Now, then. To show you how it's done...
How it's done...
How do we do that, exactly?
You didn't think about what to show her, huh?
Japanese romance? I mean...
What should we show her, exactly?
We hit the jackpot!
What do you think, Fujinomiya-san?
I think Masamune-sama might
enjoy this level of sweetness.
Yeah, you're right.
Fujinomiya-san, do you
still like Masamune-kun?
Huh? Huh?!
Is that a bit too pathetic
after he rejected me?
Not at all! Really!
Sometimes, I think about what could've been.
Perhaps if we had met in
a slightly different way...
Maybe if there wasn't a lie
involved from the start...
But if I didn't have that lie,
I would've been too scared to approach him.
I'm sure he's going to suffer
even more from now on.
Just like me.
I'm sort of looking forward
to that day, but also not.
It's rather complicated.
I can't really understand complicated things,
b-but since you're so confused
by this, Fujinomiya-san...
I think you're very profound!
Thank you very much, Kojuurou-san.
What lovely words of encouragement.
I'm such a loser.
Oh?
Is something the matter?
Maybe I'm seeing things...
Yeah, I think I am.
Hey, is this really the right way?
I think we got it right this time. I'm sorry.
Aki-chan wanted to tell me
something personally, right?
I can't keep her waiting, then.
Sorry. Just a little farther.
Until free time is over...
You just keep apologizing over and over.
Hey. Are you hiding something from me?
I'm sorry.
I was actually lying when I said
Aki-sama was waiting for you.
What? Why would you lie
about something like that?
Because... I wanted to spend as much time
with you as I could, Kanetsugu-sama.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Kanetsugu-sama.
O-Oh, jeez...
Yeah, right.
I'm not gonna fall for that anymore,
you betraying little witch.